# **David Wesseling**

London, England, United Kingdom



linkedin.com/in/david-wesseling-a511748a



david.wesseling1@gmail.com

## Summary

I'm a self-taught developer seeking my first professional junior development role. About 2 years ago I discovered I had a passion for programming and since then I've been spending every spare moment learning as much as I can. At present my primary language is C# but recently I've been using HTML5 and CSS quite a bit.

Check out some of my projects on my portfolio at deign77.github.io

## **Experience**



## Assistant Facilities Manager

Bloomsbury Publishing Plc

May 2014 - Present (6 years 4 months +)



#### Reception Coordinator

Portico

Mar 2013 - Jan 2014 (11 months)

In this position I was part of a small team responsible for front and back of house services for the London branch of Bristol-based law firm Burges Salmon LLP. My role varied slightly from that of the receptionists but overlapped in most areas. My responsibilities included:

- # Meeting room booking and setup
- # Event Planning and Management
- # Hospitality & Catering
- # Liaising with various contractors & service providers including taxis, couriers, catering, office supply, florists, etc.
- # Answering and transferring incoming calls & emails as appropriate

I was also personally responsible for the management of the store rooms, wine cellar and kitchens, including stock ordering

## **₩** Supervisor

ITV

Oct 2010 - Oct 2012 (2 years 1 month)

In this role, the number of staff had been reduced and there was no longer a manager to support. Instead I was the sole person responsible for the day to day running of the café with only some light supervision from the general manager.

My duties were similar to the last time I held the position, only with more time spent on office and administrative tasks and working more closely with the general manager.

## **₩** Supervisor

ITV

May 2008 - Sep 2009 (1 year 5 months)

This position was in a café which was one of several sites in The London Studios building in Southwark and managed by contract catering company Baxter Storey. The role saw me supporting the manager of the café in his day-to-day duties and running the place during his absences and holidays. My responsibilities included:

- # Stock room management and ordering
- # Cashier duties
- # Staff Management incl. training, creating rotas, etc.
- # Health & Safety compliance
- # Liaising with clients, suppliers, senior management, etc.
- # Basic Office Duties (incl. use of MS Excel, Word, Outlook)

#### **Supervisor**

**Elior Group** 

Apr 2007 - May 2008 (1 year 2 months)

#### **Education**



#### **CVA College**

2002 - 2006

#### Skills

Time Management • Customer Service • Administrative Assistants • Outlook • Facilities Management • Office Administration • Office Management • Telephone Skills • Administration • Data Entry